<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<languages>
	<language name="en" id="en">
		<contenttypes>
			<page>
				<title>Welcome to Khoa's Site</title>
			</page>
			<homepage>
				<properties>
					<header>
						Khoa learn to build website using Optimizely CMS
					</header>
					<body>
						Click About for more info
					</body>
				</properties>
			</homepage>
			<aboutpage>
				<properties>
					<header>
						Table of content
					</header>
					<body>
						<![CDATA[
						<ul>
						<li>Installation: Run cmd as administrator, then use command line to install the Optimizely templates and install the Episerver CLI Tool.</li>
						<li>Page Types: A website is a set of pages, one page is linked with one url, content of page is html.</li>
						<li>Block Types: Block is a partial view, block does not link to any url, block located inside a page (or another block)</li>
						<li>Template Resolver: In an Episerver website, a page URL does not map to a specific controller and an action method. 
						Instead, the Url maps to a virtual page stored within the Episerver database.
						When a request comes in, the template resolvers job is to find the correct template to use for that request.</li>
						<li>TemplateDescriptor is an optional attribute that registers templates, and is involved when the system determines which template to use when rendering a content.</li>
						<li>EPiServer.Web.DisplayChannel is a base class that is used for creating display channels, to detect viewport settings, and select templates to render content for a targeted device (desktop, tablet, mobile).</li>
						<li>We can config DisplayOptions  to choose how the content should be laid out (full, wide, narrow).</li>
						<li>Episerver Forms is an add-ons, support multi-step actions for website users to do event registrations, job applications, customer surveys.</li>
						<li>TinyMCE is a rich-text editor that allows users to create formatted content within a user-friendly interface.</li>
						<li>Media inherits from MediaData is a type content (like pages, blocks), it's content is structured in binary, for example media of type images, video, and text or PDF files.</li>
						<li>Blob: unstructured data (file chunk, a fragment of information which is used in many media).</li>
						<li>Globalization and Localization.</li>
						<li>Scheduled Job</li>
						</ul>
						]]>
					</body>
				</properties>
			</aboutpage>
			<contactpage>
				<properties>
					<header>
						Contact Me
					</header>
					<body>
						khoa.nguyen@niteco.se
					</body>
				</properties>
			</contactpage>
			<mediapage>
				<properties>
					<header>
						Demo block and media
					</header>
					<body>
						Image goes here
					</body>
				</properties>
			</mediapage>
		</contenttypes>
	</language>
	<language name="nl" id="nl">
		<contenttypes>
			<page>
				<title>Welkom op de site van Khoa</title>
			</page>
			<homepage>
				<properties>
					<header>
						Khoa bouwt website met behulp van Optimizely CMS
					</header>
					<body>
						Klik op Over voor meer informatie
					</body>
				</properties>
			</homepage>
			<aboutpage>
				<properties>
					<header>
						Inhoudsopgave
					</header>
					<body>
						<![CDATA[
						<ul>
						<li>Installatie: Voer cmd uit als beheerder en gebruik vervolgens de opdrachtregel om de Optimizely-sjablonen te installeren en de Episerver CLI Tool te installeren.</li>
						<li>Paginatypen: Een website is een reeks pagina's, één pagina is gekoppeld aan één URL, de inhoud van de pagina is html.</li>
						<li>Bloktypes: Blok is een gedeeltelijke weergave, blok linkt niet naar een URL, blok bevindt zich binnen een pagina (of een ander blok)</li>
						<li>Sjabloonoplosser: Op een Episerver-website verwijst een pagina-URL niet naar een specifieke controller en een actiemethode.
						In plaats daarvan verwijst de URL naar een virtuele pagina die is opgeslagen in de Episerver-database.
						Wanneer er een verzoek binnenkomt, is het de taak van de sjabloonoplossers om het juiste sjabloon te vinden dat voor dat verzoek kan worden gebruikt.</li>
						<li>TemplateDescriptor is een optioneel attribuut dat sjablonen registreert en wordt betrokken wanneer het systeem bepaalt welke sjabloon moet worden gebruikt bij het weergeven van inhoud.</li>
						<li>EPiServer.Web.DisplayChannel is een basisklasse die wordt gebruikt voor het maken van weergavekanalen, het detecteren van viewport-instellingen en het selecteren van sjablonen om inhoud weer te geven voor een gericht apparaat (desktop, tablet, mobiel).</li>
						<li>We kunnen DisplayOptions configureren om te kiezen hoe de inhoud moet worden opgemaakt (volledig, breed, smal).</li>
						<li>Episerver Forms is een add-on die acties in meerdere stappen ondersteunt voor websitegebruikers om evenementregistraties, sollicitaties en klantonderzoeken uit te voeren.</li>
						<li>TinyMCE is een rich-text-editor waarmee gebruikers opgemaakte inhoud kunnen creëren binnen een gebruiksvriendelijke interface.</li>
						<li>Media die overerven van MediaData zijn een type-inhoud (zoals pagina's, blokken). De inhoud is binair gestructureerd, bijvoorbeeld media van het type afbeeldingen, video en tekst- of PDF-bestanden.</li>
						<li>Blob: ongestructureerde gegevens (bestandsfragment, een informatiefragment dat in veel media wordt gebruikt).</li>
						<li>Globalisering en lokalisatie.</li>
						<li>Geplande taak.</li>
						</ul>
						]]>
					</body>
				</properties>
			</aboutpage>
			<contactpage>
				<properties>
					<header>
						Neem contact met mij op
					</header>
					<body>
						khoa.nguyen@niteco.se
					</body>
				</properties>
			</contactpage>
			<mediapage>
				<properties>
					<header>
						Demoblok en media
					</header>
					<body>
						Afbeelding komt hier
					</body>
				</properties>
			</mediapage>
		</contenttypes>
	</language>
</languages>
